A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.30 (A2004) FA482
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2004.080: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2004.080; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3699-R3700.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3699-R3700.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.080.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99009 #211 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION (BELGIUM) - SEMINAR ON FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAMS IN 21ST CENTURY, 1999-2001 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99012 #216 - SITE SANTA FE - THIRD INTERNATIONAL BIENNIAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99012 #217 - QUEENS COUNTY ART AND CULTURAL CENTER - CURATORIAL PLANNING MEETING FOR EXHIBITION, "GLOBAL CONCEPTUALISM/LOCAL CONTEXTS", 1996-1999 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99012 #218 - NEW MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - EXHIBITION, "TIME OF OUR LIVES", 1999-2000 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99012 #219 - ART IN GENERAL - EXHIBITION OF WORK OF CECILIA VICUNA, 1998-1999 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99012 #22 - 6 GUGGENHEIM FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION, "THE WORLDS OF NAM JUNE PAIK", 1999-2001 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #222 - KATONAH MUSEUM OF ART - EXHIBITION, "REFLECTIONS OF TIME AND PLACE", 1998-2000 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #223 - MATTRESS FACTORY - SITE-SPECIFIC INSTALLATIONS BY ASIAN ARTISTS, 1998-2003 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #224 - NEW MEXICO STATE UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION, "EL FAVOR DE LOS SANTOS?", 1998-2004 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #225 - TUFTS UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION OF CHICANA ALTER-INSPIRED ART, 1996-2004 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #227 - INSTALLATION GALLERY - ARTISTS PROJECTS DEVELOPED AT "INSITE 2000", 1999-2004 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #228 - INDEPENDENT CURATORS INTERNATIONAL - EXHIBITION, "BEYOND PRECONCEPTIONS: THE SIXTIES EXPERIMENT", 1999-2002 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #229 - LOWER EAST SIDE TENEMENT MUSEUM - "SONGS OF THE SWEATSHOP", 1998-2000 (Box R3700)
    - RF 99012 #230 - MUSEUM FOR AFRICAN ART - EXHIBITION, "STATUS, SYMBOL AND STYLE: HAIR IN AFRICAN ART AND LIFE, 1999-2000 (Box R3700)